Hey, you guys know what sounds weird? Eggnog.
嘿  伙计们你们知道什么听起来或怪异吗  鸡蛋酒
Eggnog?
-鸡蛋酒
Yeah, nog, what is a nog?
没错 nog  什么是nog
-Nog? You mean like "nogging"? -No, nog. Like...like "fog" or "bog".
-Nog  你是说像nogging发音  -不是nog  像是fog或bog
Nog!
Nog
No, no . it's like the nog that's found inside of an egg, it's got a lot of protein.
不不  好像nog是在鸡蛋里发现的  富含蛋白质
Whoa!
哇哦
-Hey, guys! -Um, why are you outrageously bright?
-嘿  伙计  -嗯  为什么你会不同寻常地闪亮
Oh, well, this happens every time I take a bath, it'll wear off. We're talking about eggnog over here?
哦 好吧  每次我洗完澡后就会这样  这很快就会消失的  我们回到蛋酒的话题吧
-Whoa! I can still see you with my eyes closed. -That little twerp is making my eyes bleed.
-哇哦  我闭上眼睛都可以看到你  -那个傻逼把我的眼睛都弄出血了
-Seriously. It's like staring at the sun. -Oh, no! I'm melting! Aaaahh!
-说实话  就像是盯着太阳  -我要融化了  啊啊啊
Geez, sorry, guys.
上帝啊  对不起  大伙
I guess I'll just go away.
我还是走开好了